hifisoundconnection.com 2010-08-25

# HiFiSoundConnection.com - Privacy Policy

|   
---  
| Car Audio  
| Car Audio Accessories  
| Closeouts  
| Home Theater  
| Home Theater Accessories  
| Marine Audio  
| Mobile Video  
| Pro Audio  
| Pro Lighting  
| Satellite Radio  
  
[Reviews, Guides  
& How-To's](http://www.hifisoundconnection.com/Shop/Control/fp/SFV/30046/view_page/Reviews_Guides_How-Tos)

| 

|  **Privacy Statement for hifisoundconnection.com**  
HiFiSoundconnection.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: hifisoundconnection.com 

  * Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. 
  * This site contains links to other sites. hifisoundconnection.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 
  * Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

---  
**Public Forums**  
  
  * This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
  
  * This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
  
  * Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 
  * This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [**sales@hifisoundconnection.com**](mailto:sales@hifisoundconnection.com)  
  
|
